Guide to the photograph album 'Egypt and Sudan Post Card Album' compiled by Edith and William P. Lincoln - Hisham Khatib Collection AD.MC.030_ref165
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- 'Egypt and Sudan Post Card Album' compiled by Edith and William P. Lincoln - Hisham Khatib Collection, 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165; Lincoln, Edith; Lincoln, William P. (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_MC_030_ref165)
  - From the top left clockwise: A man holding a donkey, the Temple of Kom Ombo from afar, a man leaning on columns while holding a sword, and a postcard (No. 1579) showing a relief of the crowning of Philomete in the Temple of Kom Ombo., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000090_000001; Unknown; 1 Pho
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Individual Portraits; Men; Regional/National Dress; Fez/Tarboush; Hats; Workers; Uniforms; Donkeys; Animals; Women; Head Covers/Veils; Flags; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings; Nile River; Rivers; Statues/Sculptures; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Swords/Knives; Weapons; Facial Hair
  - Two postcards. Top: (No. 1537) The bath of Cleopatra, with the Island of Elephantine in the background, Aswan. Bottom: A view of the Island of Elephantine showing the Gateway of Alexander the Great., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000091_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Men; Individual Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Water; Aswan, Egypt; Buildings; Palm Trees; Camlica Hill, Istanbul, Turkey; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Nile River; Rivers; Architecture
  - Top: A clipping entitled 'Upper-Egypt Assouan.' Bottom: (No. 1536) A postcard of boats near Aswan, seen from Elephantine Island., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000092_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Aswan, Egypt; Printed Materials; Photographic Prints; Postcards; Gelatin Silver Prints; Temples; Architecture; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Water; Nile River; Rivers; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Men; Group Portraits; Sailors; Mosques; Palm Trees; Buildings; Regional/National Dress
  - Three postcards. Top: (No. 1542) The first cataract of the Nile in Aswan. Bottom Left: (No. 1539) The entrance to the bazar in Aswan. Bottom Right: (No. 1543) A group of women and children outside their house., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000093_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Forest/Woodlands; Water; Rivers; Nile River; Landscapes; Aswan, Egypt; Streets/Roads; Markets; Mosques; Religious Sites; Men; Regional/National Dress; Shops; Group Portraits; Fez/Tarboush; Hats; Turbans; Buildings; Girls; Boys; Children; Women; Head Covers/Veils; Palm Trees; Houses
  - Two postcards: Top: (No. 1544) A view of the Cataract Hotel. Bottom: (No. 1540) A general view of Aswan., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000094_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Aswan, Egypt; Hotels; Postcards; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palm Trees; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Water; Nile River; Rivers; Buildings; Mountains/Hills; Streets/Roads; Animals; Mosques; Men; Women; Landscapes
  - Top: A postcard of the colossal statue of Rameses II in Memphis. Bottom: Two boys in rowboats in a river., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000095_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Boys; Children; Statues/Sculptures; Memphis, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Group Portraits; Individual Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Water; Rivers; Nile River; Coast; Buildings
  - Top: A view of a village. Bottom Left: (No. 1547) A woman of the Bishari tribe in her regional dress. Bottom Right: (No. 1548) A boy of the Bishari tribe., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000096_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Egypt; Boys; Children; Women; Regional/National Dress; Individual Portraits; Buildings; Mountains/Hills; Palm Trees; Jewelry; Desalination of water; Nile River; Rivers
  - Top: A view of a dam. Middle: Two views of a dam and a group portrait of men dressed in regional dress. Bottom: A postcard showing the island of Philae before the flooding., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000097_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dams/Barrages; Water; Postcards; Group Portraits; Men; Regional/National Dress; Turbans; Hats; Boys; Children; Temples; Architecture; Palm Trees; Rivers; Mountains/Hills; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Aswan, Egypt; Nile River
  - (No. 1552 and 1541) Two postcards views of the Aswan Nile dam., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000098_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Dams/Barrages; Aswan, Egypt; Water; Mountains/Hills; Nile River; Rivers; Landscapes
  - Two postcards. Top: The pylon of the Temple of Isis. Bottom: The Temple of Isis and Trajan's Kiosk., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000099_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Temples; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings; Water; Rivers; Nile River; Mountains/Hills; Landscapes; Aswan, Egypt
  - Two postcards. Top: (No. 1554) The island of Philae before the inundation. Bottom: (No.1553) The Temple of Isis before the inundation., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000100_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Nile River; Rivers; Water; Palm Trees; Landscapes; Temples; Architecture; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Aswan, Egypt
  - Two views of men on the pylons in the Temple of Isis., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000101_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Water; Nile River; Rivers; Men; Individual Portraits; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Group Portraits; Buildings; Architecture; Regional/National Dress; Turbans; Hats; Canes/Walking Sticks; Uniforms; Women; Aswan, Egypt
  - Top: (No. 1549) A postcard view of submerged Philae after the inundation. Bottom: A view of the submerged Temple of Isis., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000102_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Water; Nile River; Rivers; Men; Individual Portraits; Mountains/Hills; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Aswan, Egypt; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings
  - Top: A man holding a snake in a palm forest. Bottom: A view of temples., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000103_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Animals; Palm Trees; Countryside/Rural; Regional/National Dress; Individual Portraits; Agriculture/Farms; Landscapes; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Architecture; Aswan, Egypt
  - Top: A view of the submerged Temple of Isis. Bottom: A man handling a snake with other men behind him., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000104_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Architecture; Nile River; Rivers; Water; Animals; Regional/National Dress; Turbans; Hats; Men; Palm Trees; Countryside/Rural; Group Portraits; Aswan, Egypt
  - A blank page in the 'Egypt and Sudan Post Card Album' compiled by Edith and William P. Lincoln - Hisham Khatib Collection., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000105_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
  - Two views of crowds in a village, with an oasis in the background., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000106_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Crowds; Men; Women; Regional/National Dress; Mountains/Hills; Architecture; Head Covers/Veils; Palm Trees; Turbans; Oases; Egypt; Children
  - A blank page in the 'Egypt and Sudan Post Card Album' compiled by Edith and William P. Lincoln - Hisham Khatib Collection., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000107_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
  - Top: A landscape view of the Pyramids of Djoser in Saqqara. Bottom: A crowd in a village., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000108_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Pyramids; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Landscapes; Oases; Saqqara, Egypt; Palm Trees; Countryside/Rural; Nile River; Rivers; Water; Buildings; Crowds; Men; Turbans; Regional/National Dress; Hats; Children; Egypt
  - A blank page in the 'Egypt and Sudan Post Card Album' compiled by Edith and William P. Lincoln - Hisham Khatib Collection., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000109_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
  - A blank page in the 'Egypt and Sudan Post Card Album' compiled by Edith and William P. Lincoln - Hisham Khatib Collection., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000110_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
  - A blank page in the 'Egypt and Sudan Post Card Album' compiled by Edith and William P. Lincoln - Hisham Khatib Collection., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000111_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
  - The back cover of the 'Egypt and Sudan Post Card Album' compiled by Edith and William P. Lincoln - Hisham Khatib Collection., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000112_000001; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)